Finding Aid for Jeffrey R. Parsons papers, 1960-2013
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Correspondence, 1966-2005
  - 1990-2005
    - Clark, John 1990-1999 (Box 6)
    - Clausen, Johanna 1991 (Box 6)
    - Cobean, Robert 1990-2002 (Box 6)
    - Coe, Mike 1994 (Box 6)
    - Colegio de Michoacan 1987 (Box 6)
    - Colegio Mexiquense 1992 (Box 6)
    - Conkey, Meg 1992 (Box 6)
    - Conrad, Geoffrey 1990-1991 (Box 6)
    - Consejo Nacional de Ciencia y Tecnología (CONAYCYT) 1991-1993 (Box 6)
    - Cordova, Carlos 1982-2002 (Box 6)
    - Cornell, Per 1997-1998 (Box 6)
    - Corona, Eduardo 1994-1995 (Box 6)
    - Correa, Phyllis 1997-2002 (Box 6)
    - Cowan, Wesley 1990 (Box 6)
    - Cowgill, George 1990-2000 (Box 6)
    - Crausaz, Winston 1990-1993 (Box 6)
    - Cremonte, Beatriz 1993-2001 (Box 6)
    - Crespo, Ana María 1997 (Box 6)
    - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching-Faculty Development Fund Application 1992 (Box 6)
    - Crossland, Zoe 1995-1999 (Box 6)
    - Cuba 2002 (Box 6)
    - Culinary Historians of Ann Arbor 1992-2003 (Box 6)
    - Current Anthropology 1990-1999 (Box 6)
    - Cyphers, Ann 1981-1996 (Box 6)
    - D'Altroy, Terence 1990-2001 (Box 6)
    - Darling, Andrew 1990-2004, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Dawdy, Shannon 1997 (Box 6)
    - Delfino, Daniel D. 1995-1996 (Box 6)
    - DeMarrais, Elizabeth 1994-1996 (Box 6)
    - DeMita, Francis 1993-1995 (Box 6)
    - DeMontmillon, Olivier 1989-1994 (Box 6)
    - Descartes, Laura 1989-1994 (Box 6)
    - Diehl, Richard 1995-2000 (Box 6)
    - Dillehay, Tom 1991-2001 (Box 6)
    - Drennan, Robert D. 1990-2000 (Box 6)
    - Dumbarton Oaks 1987-1990 (Box 7)
    - Dunnavan, Sandy 1990 (Box 7)
    - Durrenburger, Paul 1984-1988 (Box 7)
    - Earle, Timothy 1993-2002 (Box 7)
    - Earls, John 1995-2002 (Box 7)
    - Early, Ann 1994 (Box 7)
    - Edelstein, Ruth 1995 (Box 7)
    - Eiselt, Sunday (B.) 2000 (Box 7)
    - Elderhostel 1995 (Box 7)
    - Emberling, Geoff 1993-1999 (Box 7)
    - Embree, Lester 1984-1988 (Box 7)
    - Erickson, Clark 1990-1998 (Box 7)
    - Erdman, Deborah 1994-1995 (Box 7)
    - Ericson, Jonathon 1995-1996 (Box 7)
    - Escott, Glenn 1998 (Box 7)
    - Evans, Susan 1990-2002 (Box 7)
    - Ewald, Ursula 1995 (Box 7)
    - Expedition-Journal University of Pennsylvania) 2002 (Box 7)
    - Faller, Lincoln 1996-1997 (Box 7)
    - Fanning, Trish 2000-2001 (Box 7)
    - Farr, Starr 1991-1997 (Box 7)
    - Farrand, William 2000 (Box 7)
    - Farrington, Ian 1994-2003 (Box 7)
    - Fauman-Tichman, R. 2001 (Box 7)
    - Fausto, Carlos 1995 (Box 7)
    - Feinman, Gary 1990-2003 (Box 7)
    - Feldman, Robert 1990-1994 (Box 7)
    - Ferriz, Horacio 1983 (Box 7)
    - Finlayson, Kerri 1994-2001 (Box 7)
    - Finsten, Laura 1989 (Box 7)
    - Fish, Suzanne and P. 1990-1999 (Box 7)
    - Fisher, Chris undated (Box 7)
    - Fitzhugh, Benjamin 1990-1997 (Box 7)
    - Flores, Fabio 2003 (Box 7)
    - Flores Ochoa, Jorge 1994 (Box 7)
    - Ford, Anabel 1993-1997 (Box 7)
    - Fossa, Lydia 1992 (Box 7)
    - Fournier, Dominique 1990 (Box 7)
    - Froschner, Richard 1996 (Box 7)
    - Garay de Fumagaldi, Mercedes 1995-2002 (Box 7)
    - Gabler, Sigrid 1991-1995 (Box 7)
    - Gacs, Utte 1980 (Box 7)
    - Gandara, Manuel 1990-1992 (Box 7)
    - Garcia, Raul 1990-1992 (Box 7)
    - Garcia, Ruben 1983-1992 (Box 7)
    - Garcia-Bacena, Joaquin 1991 (Box 7)
    - Gero, Juan 1993-1997 (Box 7)
    - Gestoso, Graciela 1994-1995 (Box 7)
    - Goland, Carol 1990-1999 (Box 7)
    - Goldenberg, Edie 1991-1997 (Box 7)
    - Goldstein, Paul 2001 (Box 7)
    - Gonlin, Nancy 1996-1997 (Box 7)
    - Gorenflo, Larry 1990-2002 (Box 7)
    - Greece-Miscellaneous 1999 (Box 7)
    - Griffin, James B. 1987-1997 (Box 7)
    - Grove, David 1992-2000 (Box 7)
    - Gudiño, Alejandra 2000 (Box 7)
    - Guerrero, Raul 1991 (Box 7)
    - Guillen, Sonia 1991-2001 (Box 7)
    - Guillet, David 1991 (Box 7)
    - Haag, William 2000 (Box 7)
    - Haber, Alejandro 1994-1998 (Box 7)
    - Hard, Robert, undated (Box 7)
    - Hare, Timothy 1997 (Box 7)
    - Hartzell, Leslie 1997 (Box 7)
    - Harvard University 1992-2002 (Box 7)
    - Harvey, Herbert 1985-1996 (Box 7)
    - Hassig, Ross 1992 (Box 7)
    - Hastings, Charles 1991-2004 (Box 7)
    - Hastorf, Christine 1986-1998 (Box 7)
    - Hayashida, Frances 1990-2001 (Box 7)
    - Healan, Dan 1990-2001 (Box 7)
    - Healy, Paul 1997 (Box 7)
    - Heffernan, Ken 1995-1997 (Box 7)
    - Helms, Mary/ Polly 1997 (Box 7)
    - Heredia, Verenice 1999-2001 (Box 7)
    - Hernandez, Benito 1990-1996 (Box 7)
    - Hicks, Frederic 1989-1994 (Box 7)
    - Hidalgo-Monroy, Neusa 1992 (Box 7)
    - Hines, Joseph 1996-2000 (Box 7)
    - Higueras, Alvaro 1998-1999 (Box 7)
    - Hirth, Kenneth 1990-2003 (Box 7)
    - Hodge, Mary 1987-1997 (Box 7)
    - Holdaway, Simon 1997-2001 (Box 7)
    - Hole, Frank 1992 (Box 7)
    - Honeychurch, William 1994-2003 (Box 7)
    - Howe, Ellen 1988 (Box 8)
    - Hopkins, Brooke 1991 (Box 8)
    - Horstman, Connie 1993 (Box 8)
    - Hoskins, Janet 1991 (Box 8)
    - Hosler, Dorothy 1990-1993 (Box 8)
    - Hudson, Jean 2002 (Box 8)
    - Human Ecology 1992 (Box 8)
    - Humphreys, Sally 1992 (Box 8)
    - Hutterer, Karl 1986-2000 (Box 8)
    - Iannone, Gyles 1991 (Box 8)
    - Iceland, Harry 1993 (Box 8)
    - Ingram, Mrill 1993-1994 (Box 8)
    - Indrisano, Gregory 2004 (Box 8)
    - Instituto de Investigaciones Antropológicas (UNAM) 1996-1997 (Box 8)
    - Instituto Nacional de Antropología e Historia (INAH) 1991-2001 (Box 8)
    - Institute of Andean Research 1990-2000 (Box 8)
    - International Institute (UM) 1993-2001 (Box 8)
    - International Union of Prehistoric and Protohistoric Sciences-Liege 2001 (Box 8)
    - Iowa University Press 1992 (Box 8)
    - Isbell, William 1993-2004 (Box 8)
    - Ives, John 1995-1996 (Box 8)
    - Jaffee, William 1990-2000 (Box 8)
    - Jakes, Catherine 1994-1995 (Box 8)
    - James, Nick 1995-1999 (Box 8)
    - Janusek, John 1994-2004 (Box 8)
    - Jimenez, Juan 1990-1991 (Box 8)
    - Johnson, Amy 1994 (Box 8)
    - Johnson, Irmgard 1991-2001 (Box 8)
    - Johnson, Laura 1990-1995 (Box 8)
    - Journal of Anthropological Archaeology undated (Box 8)
    - Journal of Anthropological Research 2002-2003 (Box 8)
    - Journal of Archaeological Science 1988-2002 (Box 8)
    - Jujuy, Universidad Nacional de (Convenio) 1995-1997 (Box 8)
    - Julien, Catherine 1998-2001 (Box 8)
    - Julien, Daniel 1994 (Box 8)
    - Junker, Laura 1990-1999 (Box 8)
    - Katz, Esther 1991-1997 (Box 8)
    - Kennedy, Diana 1992-1993 (Box 8)
    - Killion, Thomas 1992 (Box 8)
    - Kiely, Jennifer, 191 (Box 8)
    - Kim, Seung-Og 1992-1999 (Box 8)
    - Kintigh, Keith 1990-1998 (Box 8)
    - Kipnis, Renato 1999-2003 (Box 8)
    - Klausmeyer, John 1994-1995 (Box 8)
    - Klink, Cynthia 1996 (Box 8)
    - Kolata, Alan 1987-1995 (Box 8)
    - Kolb, Charles 1990-2001 (Box 8)
    - Kowalewski, Stephen 1996 (Box 8)
    - Kulemeyer, Jorge 1994-2002 (Box 8)
    - LaLone, Darrell 1991-2001 (Box 8)
    - Lambertino-Urquizo, Laurene 1990-1991 (Box 8)
    - Landis, Charles 1993 (Box 8)
    - Lane Rodriguez, Marcianna 1991 (Box 8)
    - Latin American Antiquity 1991-2002 (Box 8)
    - Laurencich, Laura 2002 (Box 8)
    - Lawson, Amy 1999-2003 (Box 8)
    - Lee, YunKuen 1993-1998 (Box 8)
    - Lemuz, Carlos 1998-2001 (Box 8)
    - Lennstrom, Heidi 1991 (Box 8)
    - Lesure, Richard 1992-2003 (Box 8)
    - Liffman, Paul 1996-2001 (Box 8)
    - Lima, Pilar 2002 (Box 8)
    - Liot, Catherine4 1994-2003 (Box 8)
    - Lippi, Ronald 1997-1999 (Box 8)
    - Litvak, Jaime 2002 (Box 8)
    - Liu, Li 2000-2001 (Box 8)
    - Livingstone, Frank 2005 (Box 8)
    - LoCelso, Marta 1999-2001 (Box 8)
    - Lopez, Olga 2003 (Box 8)
    - Lorandi, Ana Maria 1986-2001 (Box 8)
    - Lowman, Cherry 1995 (Box 8)
    - Lynch, Thomas 1992-1994 (Box 8)
    - Lyon, Patricia 1987 (Box 8)
    - MacArthur Foundation 1997 (Box 8)
    - MacCormack, Sabine 1990-1999 (Box 8)
    - Mackeres, David 1990 (Box 8)
    - MacKinnon, Jefferson J. 1991 (Box 8)
    - MacNeish, Richard 1999 (Box 8)
    - Manzanilla, Linda 1990-2001 (Box 8)
    - Marcus, Joyce 2000-2002 (Box 8)
    - Margomenou, Despina 1999-2000 (Box 8)
    - Martinez, Alejandro 1990 (Box 8)
    - Mastache, Guadalupe 1995-2000 (Box 8)
    - Mathews, Jim 1990 (Box 8)
    - Matos, Eduardo (Mexico) 2003 (Box 8)
    - Matos, Ramiro 1991-2003 (Box 8)
    - Matos, Ramiro-car problem 1986-1992 (Box 8)
    - Mayer, Enrique 1993 (Box 8)
    - Mayer-Oakes, William J. 1988-1997 (Box 8)
    - McAndrews, Tim 1998 (Box 8)
    - McCafferty, Geoffrey 1994-1997 (Box 8)
    - McEwan, Gordon 1990-1996 (Box 8)
    - McClung, Emily 1994-1995 (Box 9)
    - McCullough, John 1992-1997 (Box 9)
    - McGuire, Randall 1995 (Box 9)
    - McVicker, Donald 1990-2000 (Box 9)
    - Meggit, Mervyn (obituary) 2005 (Box 9)
    - Melville, Elinor 1993-1998 (Box 9)
    - Mexico-Instituto de Biología 1993-2001 (Box 9)
    - Mexico-13th International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences 1993 (Box 9)
    - Mexico-Miscellaneous 1993-2001 (Box 9)
    - Mexican Studies 1985-1994 (Box 9)
    - Michel, Marcos (Bolivia) 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - Michelaki, Konstantina 1995 (Box 9)
    - Michigan Archaeological Society 1993 (Box 9)
    - Michoacan, Colegio de undated (Box 9)
    - Michigan Discussions in Anthropology 2004 (Box 9)
    - Midwest Conference on Andean and Amazonian Archaeology and Ethnohistory 2001-2004 (Box 9)
    - Midwest Conference on Mesoamerican Archaeology and Ethnohistory 2002-2004 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Naomi 2001 (Box 9)
    - Minc, Leah 1993-2003 (Box 9)
    - Miner, Horace 1993 (Box 9)
    - Minnis, Paul 1990 (Box 9)
    - Mock, Shirley 1993-1995 (Box 9)
    - Moholy-Nagy, Hattula 1994 (Box 9)
    - Monaghan, John 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - Montesinos, Fanny 2001 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Emilio 1986 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Jerry 1995 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Thomas 1991-1993 (Box 9)
    - Morett, Luis 1994-2004 (Box 9)
    - Morley, Edna 1994 (Box 9)
    - Morris, Craig 1993 (Box 9)
    - Morrison, Jill 1993 (Box 9)
    - Morrison, Kathleen 1996 (Box 9)
    - Morse, Dan 1986 (Box 9)
    - Mudar, Karen Mari 1992-2001 (Box 9)
    - Mujica, Elias 1996 (Box 9)
    - Mulvaney, Eleonora 1993-2002 (Box 9)
    - Murra, John M. 1993 (Box 9)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities 1991 (Box 9)
    - National Geographic, Society 1997-2001 (Box 9)
    - National Science Foundation 1993-2000 (Box 9)
    - National Science Foundations-Panels 1980-1993 (Box 9)
    - Neely, James A. 1997-2001 (Box 9)
    - Neff, Hector 1993-2002 (Box 9)
    - Nelson, Ben A. 1990-1999 (Box 9)
    - Netherly, Patricia J. 1993-1994 (Box 9)
    - Nicholas, Linda M. 2001 (Box 9)
    - Nichols, Deborah 1990-2001 (Box 9)
    - Nielson, Axel 1992-2001 (Box 9)
    - Niles, Susan A. 1991 (Box 9)
    - Noguez, Ramirez, Xavier 1992-1993 (Box 9)
    - O'Donovan, Maria 1997-1998 (Box 9)
    - Office of the Vice President for Research UM 1993-1995 (Box 9)
    - Oklahoma Press, University of 1993-2002 (Box 9)
    - Olafsson, Gudmundur 1990-1992 (Box 9)
    - Olivera, Daniel 1995-2001 (Box 9)
    - O'Neal, Colleen 1993-1994 (Box 9)
    - Onofre, José 2001 (Box 9)
    - Orellana, Simonson, Carlos 1996 (Box 9)
    - O'Shea, John M. 1991-1998 (Box 9)
    - Ottonello, Marta 1993-2001 (Box 9)
    - Oxford University Press 1998-2000 (Box 9)
    - Palma, Jorge R. 1995 (Box 9)
    - Palme, Rudolf 1995 (Box 9)
    - Papalas, Christopher A. 1992-1995 (Box 9)
    - Parry, William undated (Box 9)
    - Parsons, Jeffrey R., American Anthropological Association-Kidder Award 1998 (Box 9)
    - Parsons, Jeffrey R., Miscellaneous 1990-2002 (Box 9)
    - Parsons, Jeffrey R., Sabbatical leaves 1992-2002 (Box 9)
    - Parsons, Jeffrey R., University of Michigan Achievement Award 2002 (Box 9)
    - Parsons, Mary 1989-1998 (Box 9)
    - Patiño Rodriguez, Héctor (Rodriguez, Héctor) 1991 (Box 9)
    - Payne, James H. 1990-1992 (Box 9)
    - Pérez, Miguel 2000-2002 (Box 9)
    - Peru-Memoir No.34 2001 (Box 9)
    - Peru, Miscellaneous 1998-2002 (Box 9)
    - Phoenix-Ford Nuclear Reactor-UM 1996 (Box 9)
    - Plenum Press 1997 (Box 9)
    - Plog, Steve 2001 (Box 9)
    - Plunket, Patricia 1997 (Box 9)
    - Pollard, Helen 1990-2002 (Box 9)
    - Poole, Deborah 1992 (Box 9)
    - Popper, Virginia 1990-2000 (Box 9)
    - Pozorski, Thomas 1990-1994 (Box 9)
    - Pulido, Salvador 1991 (Box 9)
    - Puleston, Dennis et al. 1979-2001 (Box 9)
    - Quilter, Jeffrey 1990 (Box 9)
    - Raffino, Rodolfo A. 1997 (Box 9)
    - Ramos-Elorday, Julieta 1997-2007 (Box 9)
    - Rappaport, Skip 1996-1998 (Box 9)
    - Rattray, Evelyn 1992-1995 (Box 9)
    - Reinhard, Johan 1993 (Box 9)
    - Reviews in Anthropology 1984-1986 (Box 9)
    - Ribeiro, Tony 2002 (Box 9)
    - Rice, Prudence and Don 1997-1999 (Box 9)
    - Richards, Janet 1997-2001 (Box 9)
    - Rick, John 1991-2001 (Box 9)
    - Riley, Katherine 1991 (Box 9)
    - Rinfret, Laurie 2001 (Box 9)
    - Rivera, Claudia 1998-2001 (Box 9)
    - Rivera, Mario and Ximena 1995-2003 (Box 9)
    - Rivotta, Clara 1998-2003 (Box 9)
    - Robb, John 1991-1996 (Box 10)
    - Rodriguez, Enrique 2000-2003 (Box 10)
    - Rogers, Dan 1996 (Box 10)
    - Rojas, Teresa 1994-2002 (Box 10)
    - Rolandi, Diana 1993-2001 (Box 10)
    - Roosa, William 1994 (Box 10)
    - Roselló, Lorenzo 1993-2004 (Box 10)
    - Rostworowski, María 2001 (Box 10)
    - Rowe, John 1994 (Box 10)
    - Ruiz, Marta 1995-1996 (Box 10)
    - Ruiz, Patricia 1997-1999 (Box 10)
    - Russel, Glen 1997 (Box 10)
    - Sabloff, Jeremy 1990-1991 (Box 10)
    - Sanders, William T. 1990-2002 (Box 10)
    - Sanders, William T.-Homenaje 1983-1996, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Sandweiss, Dan 1994 (Box 10)
    - Sandstrom, Alan 1993 (Box 10)
    - Santley, Robert 1994-1997 (Box 10)
    - Schjellerup, Inge 1995-2001 (Box 10)
    - Schobinger, Juan 1993 (Box 10)
    - Scholten, Robert 2000-2002 (Box 10)
    - Schreiber, Katharina 1990-2002 (Box 10)
    - Schreiner, Tom 2000 (Box 10)
    - Schroeder, Susan 1992-1997 (Box 10)
    - Schwartz, George 1990-1993 (Box 10)
    - Science 1995-2002 (Box 10)
    - Scott, Sue 1994 (Box 10)
    - Seddon, Matthew 1994 (Box 10)
    - Serra, Mari Carmen 1990-2002 (Box 10)
    - Service, Elman 1991 (Box 10)
    - Shady, Ruth 1999-2002 (Box 10)
    - Shea, Dan 1995-1996 (Box 10)
    - Sheehy, James 1996 (Box 10)
    - Sherman, Jason 1995 (Box 10)
    - Shimada, Izumi 1994-2001 (Box 10)
    - Shoocongdej, Rasmi 1999-2000 (Box 10)
    - Shott, Michael 1999 (Box 10)
    - Siemens, Alfred 1990-1991 (Box 10)
    - Sillar, Bill 1996-1998 (Box 10)
    - Silva, Jorge 1990-2003 (Box 10)
    - Silverman, Helaine 1990-2002 (Box 10)
    - Sims, Kenneth 2001-2002 (Box 10)
    - Sinopoli, Carla 1990-2002 (Box 10)
    - Sluyter, Andrew 1995 (Box 10)
    - Smart, Tristine 1997 (Box 10)
    - Smith, Adam 1998-1999 (Box 10)
    - Smith, Kevin 1995-2003 (Box 10)
    - Smith, Michael 1990-2000 (Box 10)
    - Smith, Monica 1990-2001 (Box 10)
    - Smith, Richard 1989-1991 (Box 10)
    - Smithsonian Institution 1994-1996 (Box 10)
    - Snow, Dean 2002 (Box 10)
    - Sociedad Argentina de Antropología 1994-2005 (Box 10)
    - Sociedad Mexicana de Antropología 1988-2001 (Box 10)
    - Society for American Archaeology 1997-2000 (Box 10)
    - Southern Illinois University-Carbondale 1990 (Box 10)
    - Spencer, Charles 1990-2001 (Box 10)
    - Stanish, Charles 1990-2002 (Box 10)
    - Stark, Barbara 1985-1996 (Box 10)
    - Stark, Richard 2002 (Box 10)
    - Stocker, Terry 1991-2001 (Box 10)
    - Stoddart, Simon 1991-2002 (Box 10)
    - Sugiura, Yoko 1988-1999 (Box 10)
    - Sweden-Gothenburg University 1997 (Box 10)
    - Sweden National Museum 1992-2005 (Box 10)
    - Spence, Michael 1995-1997 (Box 10)
    - Stephan, Otto E. 1995 (Box 10)
    - Stone, Glenn 1994 (Box 10)
    - Stothert, Karen 1996 (Box 10)
    - Stresser-Pan, Guy 1991-1992 (Box 10)
    - Sutter, Richard 1996-1997 (Box 10)
    - Symonds, Stacey 1990 (Box 10)
    - Taft, Mary 1991-1995 (Box 10)
    - Talalay, Lauren 1994 (Box 10)
    - Tarrago, Myriam 1995 (Box 10)
    - Tartusi, Marta and Victor Núñez 1995-2004 (Box 11)
    - Terrenato, Nicola 1995-1999 (Box 11)
    - Texas University Press 1988-2002 (Box 11)
    - Thomas, Brooke 1998-2001 (Box 11)
    - Thomas, David H. 1997 (Box 11)
    - Thomas, Robert 1995-2000 (Box 11)
    - Thompson, Robert 1999-2002 (Box 11)
    - Tolouse University (France) 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Topic, Theresa and John 1986-1994 (Box 11)
    - Trigg, Heather 1997-2000 (Box 11)
    - Trombold, Charles 1990-2003 (Box 11)
    - Tucuman, Universidad de 1999-2000 (Box 11)
    - Tugendrajch, Philip 2000-2001 (Box 11)
    - Tulane University 1999 (Box 11)
    - Tupper, Caroline 1994 (Box 11)
    - Ullrich, Bernd 1994 (Box 11)
    - Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México (UNAM) 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA) 2000 (Box 11)
    - Urton, Gary 1992 (Box 11)
    - Utah Press, University of 1991-1999 (Box 11)
    - Valdez, Lidio 1994 (Box 11)
    - Wattemmaker, Patricia 1992-1999 (Box 11)
    - Walsh, Frank 2000-2001 (Box 11)
    - Villamil, Laura 1994-2002 (Box 11)
    - Wallrath, Matthew 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Weigand, Phil 1989-2002 (Box 11)
    - Weiss, Kenneth 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Wilke, Philip 1992 (Box 11)
    - Wilkerson, Jeffrey 1992 (Box 11)
    - Willey, Gordon 1996 (Box 11)
    - Williams, Barbara 1991 (Box 11)
    - Williams, Eduardo 1998-2003 (Box 11)
    - Williams, Veronica 1995-2000 (Box 11)
    - Wilson, David 1991-2000 (Box 11)
    - Wing, Elizabeth 1994 (Box 11)
    - Winterhalder, Bruce 1985 (Box 11)
    - Wobst, Martin 1991 (Box 11)
    - Wolf, Eric R. 1986-1999 (Box 11)
    - Wright, Henry T. 1990-1997 (Box 11)
    - Yacobaccio, Hugo 1995 (Box 11)
    - Yaeger, Jason 1990-2001 (Box 11)
    - Yamamoto, Mayumi 1992 (Box 11)
    - Yoffee, Norman 1993-2001 (Box 11)
    - Zeitlin, Robert 1984-1997 (Box 11)
    - Zinn, Ann 2001 (Box 11)
- Archaeological Sites and Projects 1966-2010
  The Archaeological Sites and Projects, 1966 - 2010 series (19.25 linear feet) document Parsons' field research, mainly doing systematic settlement pattern surveying. This is the largest series in the collection. Materials included are the product of survey research on each site and consist of site reports, field notebooks, surveys, photos, and additional documentation about the sites and the research carried out. The series is made up of eight subseries and arranged by archaeological site and year and include sites in the Valley of Mexico and Peru. The subseries included are Texcoco 1967, Chalco 1969, Ixtapalapa 1969, Chalco-Xochimilco 1972, Zumpango 1973, Mexico Ceramic Surveys, Ethnographic Field Research, and Peru 1996-2010. Survey Site Reports are labeled by site number and survey strip and provide information on the natural setting of the site, modern cultural features, prehistoric features, as well as a summary and impressions on the site. Site report files regularly include photographic contact prints of the site illustrating the information gathered and include references to geographical location, roll number and shot. Additional materials per site may hold reports, maps, population data, illustrations, keys to survey materials and quantitative information.
  - Texcoco 1967
    The Texcoco 1967 subseries contains 2.5 linear feet of site reports, site notebooks, files on provenience, a number of air photos, as well as data on ceramic material, meteorological conditions and tlatel sites. Field Notebook and sites data was gathered by Mary Hrones, Douglas Price, Richard Blanton, Jeffrey Parsons, and Robert Hirning.
    - Site Reports
      - Texcoco Urban Center (Box 11)
      - Completed Photos-Strip I (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-1(I) 1:25,000 photo (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-2 (I) 1:25,000 photo (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-3 (I) 1:25,000 photo (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-4 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-5 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-6 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-7 (I) H-14 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-8 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-9 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-10 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-11 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-12 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-13 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-14 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-15 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-16 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-17 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-18 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-19 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-20 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-21 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-22 (I) Tx-LA-24 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-23 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-24 (I) Tx-LA-40 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-25 (I) Tx-LA-40 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-26 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-27 (I) Tx-LA-24 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-28 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-29 (I) Tx-LA-26 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-30 (I) Tx-LA-27 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-31 (I) Tx-LA-28 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-32 (I) Tx-LA-25 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-33 (I) Tx-A-38 Tx-A-39 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-34 (I) Tx-A-35 Tx-A-36 Tx-A-37 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-35 (I) Tx-A-32 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-36 (I) Tx-A-31 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-37 (I) Tx-A-30 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-38 (I) Tx-A-34 (Box 11)
      - Tx-A-40 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-1 (I) 1:25,000 photo (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-2 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-3 (I) 1:25,000 photo (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-4 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-5 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-6 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-7 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-8 (I) Tx-ET-7 (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-9 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-10 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-11 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-12 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-13 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-14 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-15 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-16 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-17 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-18 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-19 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-20 (I) (Box 11)
      - Tx-T-21 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-22 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-23 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-24 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-25 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-26 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-27 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-28 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-29 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-30 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-31 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-1 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-2 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-3 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-4 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-5 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-1 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-2 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-3 (I) Tx-TF-10 (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-4 (I) Tx-TF-4 (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-5 (I) Tx-TF-4 (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-6 (I) Tx-TF-4 (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-7 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-8 (I) Tx-TF-6 (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-9 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-10 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-11 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-12 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-13 (I) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-14 (I) Tx-TF-2 (Box 12)
      - Tx-Q-1 (I) (Box 12)
      - Miscellaneous Photos 1967 (Box 12)
      - General Survey-Texcoco Region 1967 (Box 12)
      - Tamuin, San Luis Potosí-Brief Survey & Impressions 1967 (Box 12)
      - Amelucan, Puebla 1967 (Box 12)
      - Texcoco Region-Modern Occupation (Box 12)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
      - Texcoco Region-Houseplan Provenience (Box 12)
      - Texcoco Region-Ceramic Provenience (Box 12)
      - Texcoco Region Survey-Photo Plate Proveniences (Box 12)
      - Strip I-Tlatel (site) Lists and Map Keys 1967 (Box 12)
      - Strip I-Miscellaneous Photos (Box 12)
      - Strip II and IIC-Site No.5 and Associated Tlatels and Locations 1967 (Box 12)
      - Traced Photos (no sites) Strip II (Box 12)
      - Strip III-Indices and Tables 1967 (Box 12)
      - Texcoco region-Correlation Between Field Number and Report Number (Box 12)
      - Aztec Site Locations and Ceramic Characteristics (Box 12)
      - Temperature and Rainfall Averages 1962-1966 (Box 12)
      - Tx-Q-1 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-1 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-2 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-3 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-4 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-5 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-6 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-7 (II-C) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-8 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-9 (II) (Box 12)